[{"answer": " Mom, Im a little worried about college.  I just dont know what to study.  I don", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " That can be a tough decision, Kate", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Mom, Im a little worried about college.  I just dont know what to study.  I don", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " How can I decide", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 17, "question": " That can be a tough decision, Kate", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Well, Id start with your interests.  It will help if you study something that you ar", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 18, "question": " How can I decide", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " I guess I like dancing and helping people.  Those are my interests I guess", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Well, Id start with your interests.  It will help if you study something that you ar", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " What do you mean by helping people", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 23, "question": " I guess I like dancing and helping people.  Those are my interests I guess", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " If people have problems, I like to help solve them.  Or if people are hurt I like t", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 24, "question": " What do you mean by helping people", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " It sounds like you might be interested in counseling or medicine then", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 28, "question": " If people have problems, I like to help solve them.  Or if people are hurt I like t", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " UhI dont know", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 29, "question": " It sounds like you might be interested in counseling or medicine then", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " What about dancing", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 33, "question": " UhI dont know", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " I just like to dance", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 34, "question": " What about dancing", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Maybe you could be a professional dancer", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 35, "question": " I just like to dance", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " That would be so sweet", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Maybe you could be a professional dancer", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Another thing I think you should consider is the possible jobs you might get an", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 37, "question": " That would be so sweet", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": "How do I figure that out", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Another thing I think you should consider is the possible jobs you might get an", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " You can research different occupations at the library and there are lots of publi", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 42, "question": "How do I figure that out", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Hmmm.  I know that is hard to make it as a professional dancer.  But, if you do", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 46, "question": " You can research different occupations at the library and there are lots of publi", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Well maybe you can research what the average dancer makes in the U.S.  No", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Hmmm.  I know that is hard to make it as a professional dancer.  But, if you do", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Me neither.  I guess Ill have to look that up too", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Well maybe you can research what the average dancer makes in the U.S.  No", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " That will give you an idea of the possible money you can make and you can the", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Me neither.  I guess Ill have to look that up too", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " I want to make lots of money.  I want to be able to travel a lot", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 59, "question": " That will give you an idea of the possible money you can make and you can the", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Well, there you go.  Potential salary is going to affect your major choice.  Ther", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 60, "question": " I want to make lots of money.  I want to be able to travel a lot", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Whats that", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Well, there you go.  Potential salary is going to affect your major choice.  Ther", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Financial aid.  You know scholarships and grants", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Whats that", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " What does my major have to do with that", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Financial aid.  You know scholarships and grants", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Well, with some majors there are more opportunities to get financial aid.  Som", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 67, "question": " What does my major have to do with that", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Oh, I see", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Well, with some majors there are more opportunities to get financial aid.  Som", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " So, you might want to pick a major that will allow you to get a specia", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Oh, I see", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Yep, sure do", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 79, "question": " So, you might want to pick a major that will allow you to get a specia", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " I know youll make the right decision.  Just consider all of this information an", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Yep, sure do", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Thanks, mom", "docId": "04-03", "aSentId": 84, "question": " I know youll make the right decision.  Just consider all of this information an", "qSentId": 83}]
